Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1879-1948; 121.0 boxes
  - Subseries 2A: General, 1885-1948; 101.0 boxes
    - Philadelphia Saving Fund Society, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Philadelphia School District Superintendent, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Philadelphia School of Design for Women, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Philadelphia Sesqui-Centennial, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27a)
    - Philadelphia [Sinfonietta] Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Philadelphia Sketch Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Philadelphia Suburban Gas & Electric Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Philadelphia Suburban Publishing, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Philadelphia Tapestry Mills, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Philadelphia Tresurer's Office, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Philadelphia Vacant Lots Cultivation Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Philips, Melville, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Phillips, Edward B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Phillips, James, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Philobiblon Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Philomathean Society, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Philomusician Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Photographers re: European Pictures, 1891-1892; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Pictoral Review, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Pierce, Harold, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Pierce, J. D. [John Denton], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Pierce, S. A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Pierce, S. S. & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Pierson, Ward W. and Harold S. Shertz, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Pilling & Crane, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Pillsbury, Eleanor, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Pillsbury, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Pincus, Edythe, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Pincus, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Pincus, S. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Pincus, Walter, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Pindell, Edith C. S. [Mrs. D. S. Pindell], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Pitcarin, Raymond, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Pitman, Raymond A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Pitney, Hardin & Skinner, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - Pittsburgh Coal Producers Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Pitz, Henry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 60)
    - The Plastic Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Platt, Elizabeth [Mrs. Charles Platt, Jr.], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - The Players, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Plays and Players, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Pleasant Mills/Batsto History, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Plimpton, George, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Plub, Ralph H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Plunkett, William H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Pocock, J. J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Poet-Lore, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Poetry, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Poetry House, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - The Poetry Society of America, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Poet's House, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Polak, J. Marcus, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Police Veterans Association of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Pollock, Porter, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Pomerantz, A & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Pond, J. B. Lyceum Bureau, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Pool, Charles L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Poole, Abram, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Poole, Samuel T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Poor, Mrs. D. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Poore, Henry Rankin, 1888-1937; 2.0 folders (Folder 25-26)
    - Porter, George D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Porter, Rose, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Portland Society of Art, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Portsmouth, The Countess of, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Post, Louis F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Postal-Telegraph-Cable Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Pote, Albert H. Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - The Potter Coal & Coke Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Potter, L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Potter, Virginia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Potter, William J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Pottinger, David T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Potts, Theodore R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Potts, Thomas C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Powel, Hartford W. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Powell, John, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Powell, Lyman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Powell, M. E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Powers & Magee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Pratt, S. F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Prentiss, G. A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Prentzel, S. F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Presbyterian Church, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - The Press, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Press Intelligence Bureau, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - The Presser Foundation, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Prestion & Rounds Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Pretlow, Fannie, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Price, Waterhouse & Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Prichard, Frank P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Prichard, Louise Heald, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Prichard, Saul, Bayard & Evans, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Print Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Priscilla Guthrie's Book Shop, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Proctor, A. P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Progress and Poverty, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Prohibition, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Pro-League Independents, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Prophet, N. Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - The Providence Journal, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Providence Ornamental Iron Works, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Providence, R. I. Public Library, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Providence Telphone Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Providence Washington Insurance Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - The Provident Life & Trust Company of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Pruyer, Mary L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Pruyer, N. K., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Pryor, Roy T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28a)
    - Public Archives Commission of Delaware, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Public Charities Association of Philadelphia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Public Ledger, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Publishers' & Booksellers' Association, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Publishers' Rejections & Acceptances of Poetry and Prose, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Puff, Charles Frederick, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Pulitzer, Ralph, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Pullinger, Herbert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - The Pullman Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Punch, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Purdune, Beatrice Stevenson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Purdy, W. Frank, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - The Puritan Club, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Putnam, George Haven, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Putnam, Herbert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Putnam, S. A. Brock, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Putnams Books, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Pyle, Howard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Pyle, Walter L., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - The Quaker, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Quatrich, Bernard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Quarles, H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Quiet May, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Quigley, John A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Quigley, Mary, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - The Quill Book Shop, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Quinn, Edmond T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Quinton, Cornelia B. Sage, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Rabbinical Assembly of America, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Raditz, Lazard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Raffaelli, Jean Francis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Railway Express Agency, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Rainey, Roy A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Ralston, Virgnia Louis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Rambo, Ormond, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Ramsey, Charles F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Ramsey, William M, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - The Rand School of Social Science, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Randall, B. Alexander, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Randle, William H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Randolph, Mary Durham, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Ranger, H. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Rapp, Sarah Mushumer von, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Rapp, William R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Rathburn, Gertrude H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Raymond, Nelson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Read, Philip H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Reading Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Reading-New Jersey Central, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Reading Railway, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Reazor, Frank B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Red Cross, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Red Star Line, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33a)
    - Reder, O., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Redfield, Edward W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Redwod Library and Athenaeum--Newport, Rhode Island, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Reed, David A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Reed, Jacob & Sons, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Reese, Lizette Woodworth, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 39-40)
    - Reeves, Admiral, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Reeves, Robert C. Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Regan's Express Moving, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Regester, Helen Wilson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Rehn, Frank K. M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Reichard, Edward, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Reid, Robert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Reilly, Horace, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Reinhardt, Marie A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Reinhard, H. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Reisinger, Hugo, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Reiss, Wihold, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Relief Fund for the Families of French Soldiers-Artists, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Remine, Sue, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Remington, Frederic, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Remington Typewriter Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Rendall, Stanley, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Rennell, Lord, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Renshaw, Lloyd, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Replogle, J. Leonard, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Replogle Steel Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Republican Independent Citizens' Committee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Republican League, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Republican State (Pennsylvania) Committee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Republicans for Roosevelt League, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Revuling, George, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - The Review of Reviews, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Rex, William C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Reyburn, John E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Reynolds, Katherine, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Reynolds, Paul R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Rhawn, William H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Rhawnhurst Construction Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Rhead, Louis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Rhein, Elizabeth Kane [Mrs. John H. W. Rhein], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Rhoades, S. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Rhoads, Charles J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Rhoads, Harriet [Mrs. E. Clinton Rhoads], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Rhoads, Lillie [Mrs. Charles J. Rhoads], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Rhoads, Harry P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Rhoads, Lydia Wistar & Ethel Rhoads, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Rhode Island Board of Public Roads, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Rhode Island Department of Agriculture, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Rhode Island--Governor, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Rhode Island Philosophical Society, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Rhode Island Public Health Commission, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Rhode Island Real Estate Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Rhode Island School of Design, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Rhode Island State Board of Agriculture, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Rhode Island State Board of Health, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Rhode Island State board of Public Roads, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Rhode Island State College, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - The Rhode Island Tercentenary Jubilee Committee, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 40)
    - Rhodes, Arthur J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 41)
    - Rhodes, James F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 42)
    - Rhodes, L. D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 43)
    - Ricardo, Grazia, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 44)
    - Rice, Cale Young, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 45)
    - Rice, Lita Angelica, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 46)
    - Richards, A. M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 47)
    - Richards, G. Whitfield Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 48)
    - Richards, Theodore William, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 49)
    - Richards, William T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 50)
    - Richardson, Aaron R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 51)
    - Richardson, James Edward, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 52)
    - Richardson, James G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 53)
    - Richardson, J. M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 54)
    - Richmond Garage, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 55)
    - Richter, W. S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 56)
    - Rider-Ericsson Engine Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 57)
    - Ridgely, Mrs., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 58)
    - Ridgely, Lawrence B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 59)
    - Ridgway, Thomas, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 60)
    - [Ridu], M. G. B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 61)
    - Riesman, David, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 62)
    - Riley, James Whitecomb, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 63)
    - Ring, G. Oram, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 64)
    - "A Ripping Tale", dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 65)
    - Ritchie, Mary D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 66)
    - Riter, Frank M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Rittenberg, Henry R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Rittenhouse, Charles A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Ritz-Carlton Hotel, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Robbins, E. C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Robbins, Mary C., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Roberts, Alice Mumford, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Roberts, Charles G. D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Roberts, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 9-10)
    - Roberts, Ina Brevoort, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Roberts, Mrs. Owen J., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Roberts, T., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Wm. T. B. & Son, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Robertson, Edward & Elizabeth Robertson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Robertson, O. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Robins, Edward & Emily Robins, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Robins, H. R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Robins, Thomas Ellis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Robinson, Alexander, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Robinson, Dan, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Robinson, [Fr.], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Robinson, Louis N., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Robinson Publishing Company, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Robinson, Thomas Pendleton, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - Robinson, William Duffield, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Robinson, William S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Rodd, Rennell, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Rodman, Julia W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Rodney Morrison & Son, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Roecker, Mary B., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Roedell, G. A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Roekens, Noel van, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Roekens, Paulette van, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - Roerich Museum, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Roeske, Otto, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Rogers, A. S., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Rogers, Benjamin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Rogers, Frank, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Rogers, Gregory, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Rogers, Joseph M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Rogers, Laussat R., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Rolshoven, Harriette [Mrs. Julius Rolshoven], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Rolshoven, Julius, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)
    - Roman Bronze Works, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 35)
    - Roman Mosaic & Tile Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 36)
    - Romanes & Paterson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 37)
    - Romeike, Albert & Company, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 38)
    - Romeike, Henry, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 39)
    - Rook, Edward F., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt & Johnson, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Roosevelt, Emily, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Roosdevelt, Theodore, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Root, Elihu, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - Roper, William W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Rose, Donald Frank, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Rose, Kate, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - Rose, Manuel Francis, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Rosenbach, A. S. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Rosenbach, Hyman, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
    - Rosengarten, F. H., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - Rosengarten, J. G., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - Rosenthal, Albert, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - [folder omitted], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
    - Rosetta Stone, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
    - Roslyn, Guy, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
    - Rotan, Samuel P., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Roth, George, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Rothert, Otto A., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
    - Rothschild, Dr., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Rousseau, S. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
    - Rowe, [L. O.], dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
    - The Royal Society of Literature, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 25)
    - Rubicam, Ida M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 26)
    - Ruckstull, F. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 27)
    - Rudge, W. E., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 28)
    - Ruff, Mary D., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 29)
    - Rumsey, Horace M., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 30)
    - Ruschenberger, C. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 31)
    - Ruse, L. W., dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 32)
    - Rush, Benjamin, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 33)
    - Rush Hospital for Consumption and Allied Diseases, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 34)